<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="Main.xsl"?>

<cancion xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="Letras.xsd">

	<titulo>Till_I_Collapse</titulo>
	<autor>Eminem</autor>
	<letra>
		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Cause sometimes you just feel tired, feel weak</verso>
			<verso>And when you feel weak, you feel like you wanna just give up</verso>
			<verso>But you got to search within you, and try to find that inner strength</verso>
			<verso>And just pull that shit out of you</verso>
			<verso>And get that motivation to not give up, and not be a quitter</verso>
			<verso>No matter how bad you wanna just fall flat on your face and collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>

		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till I collapse I'm spilling these raps long as you feel 'em</verso>
			<verso>'Till the day that I drop you'll never say that I'm not killing 'em</verso>
			<verso>'Cause when I am not, then I'ma stop penning 'em</verso>
			<verso>And I am not Hip-Hop and I'm just not Eminem</verso>
			<verso>Subliminal thoughts, when I'ma stop sending 'em?</verso>
			<verso>Women are caught in webs, spin 'em and hock venom</verso>
			<verso>Adrenalin shots, the penicillin could not get the illing to stop</verso>
			<verso>Amoxicillin's just not real enough</verso>
		</estrofa>

		<estrofa>
			<verso>The criminal cop-killing hip hop villain</verso>
			<verso>A minimal swap to cop millions of Pac listeners</verso>
			<verso>You're coming with me, feel it or not you're gonna fear it</verso>
			<verso>Like I showed you the spirit of God lives in us</verso>
			<verso>You hear it a lot, lyrics to shock</verso>
			<verso>Is it a miracle or am I just product of pop fizzing up?</verso>
			<verso>For shizzle my wizzle, this is the plot, listen up</verso>
			<verso>You bizzles forgot, Slizzle does not give a fuck!</verso>
		</estrofa>


		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>


		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>


		<estrofa>
			<verso>Music is like magic, there's a certain feeling you get</verso>
			<verso>When you real and you spit and people are feeling your shit</verso>
			<verso>This is your moment, and every single minute you spend</verso>
			<verso>Tryna hold on to it 'cause you may never get it again</verso>
			<verso>So while you're in it, try to get as much shit as you can</verso>
			<verso>And when your run is over just admit when it's at its end</verso>
			<verso>Because I'm at the end of my wits with half the shit gets in</verso>
			<verso>I got a list, here's the order of my list that it's in</verso>
		</estrofa>


		<estrofa>
			<verso>It goes Reggie, Jay-Z, 2Pac and Biggie</verso>
			<verso>Andre from OutKast, Jada, Kurupt, Nas and then me</verso>
			<verso>But in this industry I'm the cause of a lot of envy</verso>
			<verso>So when I'm not put on this list, the shit does not offend me</verso>
			<verso>That's why you see me walking 'round like nothing's bothering me</verso>
			<verso>Even though half you people got a fuckin' problem with me</verso>
			<verso>You hate it but you know respect you got to give me</verso>
			<verso>The press's wet dream like Bobby and Whitney, Nate, hit me</verso>
		</estrofa>

		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>


		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
		<estrofa>
			<verso>Soon as a verse starts, I eat at an MC's heart</verso>
			<verso>What is he thinking? How not to go against me, smart</verso>
			<verso>And it's absurd, how people hang on every word</verso>
			<verso>I'll probably never get the props I feel I ever deserve</verso>
			<verso>But I'll never be served, my spot is forever reserved</verso>
			<verso>If I ever leave Earth, that would be the death of me first</verso>
			<verso>'Cause in my heart of hearts I know nothing could ever be worse</verso>
			<verso>That's why I'm clever when I put together every verse</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
		<estrofa>
			<verso>My thoughts are sporadic, I act like I'm an addict</verso>
			<verso>I rap like I'm addicted to smack like I'm Kim Mathers</verso>
			<verso>But I don't want to go forth and back in constant battles</verso>
			<verso>The fact is I would rather sit back and bomb some rappers</verso>
			<verso>So this is like a full blown attack I'm launching at 'em</verso>
			<verso>The track is on some battling raps who want some static?</verso>
			<verso>'Cause I don't really think that the fact that I'm Slim matters</verso>
			<verso>A plaque and platinum status is wack if I'm not the baddest, so</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
		<estrofa>
			<verso>'Till the roof comes off, 'till the lights go out</verso>
			<verso>'Till my legs give out, can't shut my mouth</verso>
			<verso>'Till the smoke clears out, am I high? Perhaps</verso>
			<verso>I'ma rip this shit, 'till my bone collapse</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
		<estrofa>
			<verso>Until the roof (until the roof)</verso>
			<verso>The roof comes off (the roof comes off)</verso>
			<verso>Until my legs (until my legs)</verso>
			<verso>Give out from underneath me</verso>
			<verso>I, I will not fall, I will stand tall</verso>
			<verso>Feels like no one can beat me</verso>
		</estrofa>
		
	</letra>
</cancion>